One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Let's pile up all the dreams,
And go find the thing we're looking for... One Piece!
Compasses and the like will only slow us down
Delirious with fever, let's take the helm
Even an old treasure map covered in dust...
Isn't a legend if it's been proved real!
For our own storms, all we have to do is
Ride someone else's biorythm...
And pretend that it isn't there!
Let's pile up all the dreams,
and go find the thing we're looking for...
A pocket of coins, and
We are!
Let's break the tight-fisted night!
We have no interest in treasure chests
A pocket of romance, and
We are!
Let's pile up all the dreams,
And go find the thing we're looking for...
A pocket of coins, and
We are!
Morning Comes!
The Straw Hats' Ultimate Attack!
Amazing, Straw Hat!
You defeated Oars!
Hey, Luffy! Hang in there!
Luffy!
We pushed him this far... Is he gonna be alright?
He must be completely worn out.
He was using the strength of 100 men in a single body.
Anyway, we gotta recover the shadows of all the victims quickly!
That's right!
Let's hurry!
The sky is getting brighter in the east.
It'll be morning any time now.
By the way, how do you get the shadows back?
4 of our friends were stripped off their shadows too.
That's another problem.
To tell you the truth, we wanted
Straw Hat to do that for us, but...
That'd be impossible, he can't even move right now.
Only Moriah, the master of all the shadows the zombies possess, is able to do that.
Unless he gives the "go back to your original master" order, the shadows won't return.
Let's quit the chit-chat and do it.
That's right!
We'll wake Moriah and force him to give the order.
If we don't recover the shadows, then there was no point in beating him!
O-Oars is back on his feet!
I thought that attack alone was enough to leave him unconscious!
This is terrible...
It's all over.
The entire Straw Hat crew is unconscious right now.
We've already used all the shadows we had.
We don't have anything left to defeat him with.
It doesn't hurt at all.
Damn it!
It seems we were no match for the power of a zombie after all!
We have no time left.
Dawn is almost upon us.
We'll never be freed from dwelling in darkness!
Let's give up.
We'll only find death if we stay here.
Let's go back to the forest.
Let's return... to that gloomy forest where no light can be seen.
You!
I don't know what happened to Luffy, but...
We have the upper hand right now.
H-Hey! Wait a minute, you!
If you move in that state you'll die!
He received the attack of that monster... How come he's still standing?!
I can't tell which one is the zombie here!
Hey, where did the Straw Hats we rescued go?
Don't ask me!
They couldn't have moved while being unconscious!
Huh, where are the other two?
Y-You're right!
The Long-nose and the woman are both gone.
Did they... go ahead and run off?
Huh, all of them?!
When did they...?
I-It seems it wasn't good enough.
Huh, Straw Hat!
Hey, hey, even you, Straw Hat.
I just need to give him another shot.
Damn!
I'm still worn out from before.
Robin!
Yeah.
I'm right here.
They didn't run!
I need to get up there.
Roger.
Then... I'll make you a foothold.
If there's anything I can assist you with...
Even the one reduced to bones is moving!
Why?!
Alright, Brook, I have a request!
I knew this would happen!
Everyone's ready to give you their support!
The girl from before!
Why's she there?!
Don't tell me these guys...!
Didn't intend to escape at all!
From the very moment Oars stood up...
They began to plan their counterattack!
Just watch.
Chopper, hurry up!
The sun is about to rise!
Yeah!
Is this what you needed, Franky?
That's enough, now give me a hand!
I can't believe it!
These guys never intended to give up!
Hey, you're in the way!
Step aside!
As you order!
Pierna Fleur...
Leg Flower
Here we go!
Got it!
Wait!
Where are you going?
What's this?
Smoke? Clouds?
The forecast is rain.
Coolball!
Rain Tempo!
It's raining! How come?!
Is that girl a magician?
Alright!
The emergency pipe is complete!
Damn.
Coup de Vent!
What the...?!
Spin with all your strength!
I'm on it!
Here goes!
Ultra Refrigerator Super Freezing Cannon...
Fire!
I'm frozen!
I can't move!
Amazing!
They used it to freeze the rain!
This time it's my turn!
Go!
A chain?!
Alright!
The rudder's chain?!
You're amazing, Sanji!
It was nothing!
Throw me!
Are you sure about this?!
I'll be fine, I'm a rubberman after all!
Be careful!
Gear Third!
Bone Balloon!
Zoro!
Take care of Oars' stomach!
Leave it to me!
Three Swords Style...
Secret Technique...
Three Thousand Worlds!
Now!
There you go!
Well done, Sanji!
Oars' spine is completely straight now!
What're they doing?!
The human spine is S-shaped in order to
alleviate the effects of shocks and weight.
If it's straightened out, the force isn't migitated, and all the damage is taken.
Go, Luffy!
Good luck to you!
I'll give you an extra-large bazooka!
Then, I'll counter it with my own bazooka!
Rubber...
Huh? It won't move!
My right arm won't move!
It won't stretch either!
The absence of pain is the zombie's greatest disadvantage.
He's your shadow...
Finish him off, Luffy.
Rubber...
Go!
Take him down, Straw Hat!
Heads up!
Giant...
Bazooka!
He did it!
No matter what kind of zombie he is, he can't possibly get up after that.
Oars lost.
And this time for good.
What's gonna happen to Thriller Bark?
They did it.
They're quite something.
It seems I brought some dangerous fellas...
What happened?!
Where's our Master?!
He won!
This time he really did it!
Thanks a lot!
You're the best!
As expected from our ray of hope!
This man lived up to our expectations after all!
Where's Straw Hat?
A midget!
Who're you?!
Why did you shrink?!
It doesn't hurt, and yet, I can't move.
He's still awake, despite having his bones pulverized.
How much more can this power make fun of life.
The morning sun.
Why?
What's this unease I feel...?
Hey, Luffy!
Get your shadow back, quickly!
There's no time to celebrate!
Everyone here might disappear!
The shadows!
He's right! We gotta hurry!
Now, punch that Moriah awake and
make him return all of our shadows!
The morning sun has almost risen!
There's no need...
to punch me awake.
Moriah!
Master!
I'm glad you're alright!
Moriah-sama would never fall that easily!
I-It is better now that you're awake!
Now... if you don't wanna get beaten by the Straw Hats again, you better release all of our shadows!
Yes, give 'em back, you bastard!
This isn't a child's game.
A true pirate can't be threatened with that!
If you dogs of the forest were behind this,
That solves the mystery of
Straw Hat's excessive power-up!
It's disturbing to think that
you took advantage of my shadow ability!
Shut up!
Give back the shadows!
Straw Hat, how dare you destroy my Thriller Bark!?
You were the one who messed with our trip!
Give back our shadows before the sun rises!
Had you continued on your travels in your
current state, you would have only found death!
You wouldn't have lasted a minute in the New World!
You've gathered some impressive subordinates, but...
you will lose them all!
Do you know why?!
Hey, Straw Hat, this isn't the time to chat!
Look at the sky!
It's getting brighter!
Hurry up and retrieve the shadows!
There's no time left!
I found the answer from personal experience!
Why did I lose all my skilled subordinates after they made a reputation for themselves!?
I lost my companions because they were alive!
If they're undead zombies from the very start, then you won't lose them!
Zombies are immortal!
An unlimited amount of soldiers who can be replaced at any time!
I'll use this undead army to go after the title of Pirate King once more!
You should be grateful that I chose your shadows to become my subordinates!
Something's stuck to me!
Now!
Hear my words, shadows of Thriller Bark!
Become one with my power!
Shadows' Asgard!
Asgard: heavenly residence of the gods and slain heroes in Norse mythology
Brother!
His shadow was taken.
The shadows are...!
No way!
He's gathering the shadows from the whole island and absorbing them!
Straw Hat!
You withstood 100 shadows, didn't you?!
Then, I can withstand...
200!
300!
600!
700!
1000 shadows!
It's all over.
What is that thing?
I'm back to normal.
It's nearly morning!
Even Straw Hat couldn't defeat Oars with 100 shadows.
But 10 times that amount?
So the original user can withstand a much larger amount?!
W-We're done for!
What's gonna happen now?!
This can't be true!
He absorbed Straw Hat's shadow too.
Run!
We don't stand a chance!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
He's breaking the island apart!
The mast-mansion is coming down!
Run!
Run into the forest!
This is really it!
I'm disappearing!
My body is disappearing!
Someone help me!
Fool! Hurry and get in the shade!
The sunlight is almost upon us!
Head to the forest through the shade!
Don't leave the mansion's shadow!
Captain Lola!
What're you doing?!
Hurry up!
You guys run.
What're you saying?!
You're coming with us!
I'm the one who’s responsible...
for this bet.
Look over there.
They...
Those guys...
They haven't moved an inch.
They were also stripped of their shadows.
No way!
They still think they can win?!
But he destroyed half of the island with a single blow.
Moriah's power exceeds that of Oars' right now!
Since they haven't given up yet...
I'm not moving from here.
If we keep calling them our "Ray of Hope" and then abandon them at the first sight of trouble,
we're nothing but a bunch of maggots.
But in our current situation...
You go ahead and escape.
As your Captain, I promise to uphold your honor.
You just... keep yourselves alive.
Captain Lola!
The light is reaching you!
Hurry and get in the shade!
It's okay!
This is what it means to place your hopes in other people!
Captain Lola!
No way.
Do you wanna die?!
Life or death. There's just one answer!
I don't care which one it is.
I'm not going back to the darkness!
Captain!
This is going from bad to worse.
He's completely lost it.
His rage and foolish pride are fueling his madness.
Hey, everyone, we're out of time.
This will be a bit reckless.
Alright! We're counting on you!
Take him down!
Hey, you!
What hope could you possibly have?!
There's no way you can win!
The enemy is a monster of 1000 men!
That's right!
Think this over!
He absorbed all of your shadows!
That monster is much more powerful than you!
Besides, we're out of time!
If you don't wanna get involved, just watch from there.
In this battle against Moriah, we already have the upper hand.
However,
winning before daybreak is a completely different matter.
Moriah has exceeded his limits in order to buy as much time as possible.
Gear Second!
Will we be destroyed first?
Or...
will Moriah destroy himself first?
Rubber...
Jet Rocket!
Look!
The shadows are coming out!
Jet Bazooka!
It's one after another!
Aren't those shadows supposed to be under his command?!
Moriah's control worsens as he loses consciousness!
Even for Moriah, it's impossible to handle 1000 shadows!
Rubber...
Brick Bat!
Black Box!
I'm trapped!
Disappear!
A direct hit!
The punch that divided the island!
Straw Hat!
Stop!
This is your baptism!
This is what happens to amateurs like you who try to act big in this sea!
This is what happens when you mess with a Warlord of the Sea!
Learn your place in this world!
A nail that sticks out will be hammered back into line!
Luffy-san!
Luffy!
He's back on his feet!
I don't care if I'm an amateur...
or if I'm sticking out...
No one...
can...
crush me!
No one can crush you?
The simple fact you make such baseless statements...
Shows how inexperienced you a-
Because I'm made of rubber.
I'll make you spit out all of the shadows!
What is he?
Is he immortal?!
Amazing!
Sunlight!
Damn it!
Fools! Go back to the shade!
You'll end up disappearing!
Help me!
My hand... is disintegrating!
Get in the shade!
This whole place is a dead zone!
Bone Balloon!
Hey! Is it okay to use that technique too?!
There's no way!
Did you forget that Second alone wears out your body?!
Don't be reckless, Luffy!
Your body... will be torn apart!
Rubber...
Giant...
Jet Shell!
So powerful!
The shadows are coming out!
I won't let... my army get away!
Shadows!
I am your master!
That bastard!
He's not letting the shadows get away!
My shadow!
Come back to me!
Captain Lola!
Can you hear me, shadow?!
We've been together ever since we were born!
We were born in this world together!
Please come back!
For three long years, I kept looking for the zombie in which you were trapped!
And now you're right before me, aren't you?!
If you can hear me, please come back!
Please come back!
Captain Lola!
Please take cover in the wall's shade already!
Your body could disappear!
But... it's awful.
Just when I've finally found it!
Indeed.
Right now, all of our shadows must be inside Moriah!
We're never gonna get a chance like this again!
Unfortunately, the enemy is a Warlord of the Sea.
Yes, come back!
Come back to me, shadow!
Come back!
I also have something to say to my shadow.
If you're so eager to be the Pirate King...
Hurry up and...
Come back to me!
Straw Hat, why you!
You bastard!
You will see...
In the New World... you will face the real nightmares!
In the New World...!
The shadows are returning!
H-Hey, everyone!
Hey!
Shadow! Quickly...!
Too late!